At the left we can see...
At the left we can see... 站在左边我们可以看到……
At the right we can see the...
At the right we can see the... 站在右边我们可以看到……
...the head-snarlers
...the head-snarlers ……那个怪物的头
Everything is safe. Perfectly safe.
Everything is safe. Perfectly safe. 所有的事情都很安全了 完全安全了
Emo? Emo
Emo? Emo？
Watch out!
Watch out! 当心！
Are you hurt?
Are you hurt? 你受伤了吗？
I don't think so. You?
I don't think so. You? 我觉得没有，你呢？
I'm Ok.
I'm Ok. 我很好
Get up. Emo, it's not safe here.
Get up.Emo, it's not safe here. 起来吧，这里不太安全
Let's go.
一起走吧
What's next?
下一个是什么？
You'll see!
你会看到的！
Emo. This way. Emo
Emo， 走这边！
Follow me!
跟着我！
Hurry Emo!
快！
You're not paying attention!
你怎么没有集中注意力！
I just want to answer the... ...phone.
我只是想接个…… ……个电话
Emo, look, I mean listen. emo
emo，看，听！
You have to learn to listen.
你需要来学习一下该怎么听
This is not some game.
这不是游戏
You, I mean we, we could easily die out here.
你，我们，可能很容易死在这里
Listen, listen to the sounds of the machine.
听， 听机器的声音
Listen to your breathing.
听你的呼吸
Well, don't you ever get tired of this?
那么，你对这个难道就不厌倦吗？
Tired?!?
厌倦？！？
Emo, the machine is like clockwork. Emo
Emo，这个机器就象一个精确的时钟
One move out of place...
如果一步错了……
...and you're ground to a pulp.
……你就会被碾成碎末
But isn't it -
但难道……
Pulp, Emo! Is that what you want, pulp? emo
碎末，emo！ 这是你想要的结果吗，碎末？
Emo, your goal in life...
你生活的的目标难道就是……
...pulp?
……碎末？
Emo, close your eyes. Emo
Emo，闭上你的眼睛
Why? - Now! -
为什么 - 闭上！
Ok.
好吧
Good.
很好
What do you see at your left side, Emo? Emo
你在你的左边看到了什么，Emo？
Nothing. - Really? -
没有东西 - 是吗？
No, nothing at all.
完全没有东西
And at your right, what do you see at your right side, Emo? Emo
那么在你的右边， 在你的右边能看到什么，Emo？
The same Proog, exactly the same... proog
还是一样的，proog，完全一样……
...nothing! - Great. -
……没有东西！ - 非常好
Listen Proog! Do you hear that! proog
听，proog！你听到那个声音了吗！
Can we go here?
我们能去这里吗？
There? It isn't safe, Emo. Emo
那里？那里不安全，Emo。
But... - Trust me, it's not. -
但是…… - 相信我，别去
Maybe I could...
也许，我能……
No.
不行
NO!
不行！
Any further questions, Emo? Emo
还有其他问题吗，Emo？
No.
没有了
Emo? Emo
Emo？
Emo, why...
Emo，为什么……
Emo... Emo
Emo……
...why can't you see the beauty of this place?
……为什么你不能看见 这里
The way it works.
这条路走对了
How perfect it is.
多么完美啊
No, Proog, I don't see. Proog
对，Proog，我没有看见
I don't see because there's nothing there.
我没有看见是因为那里空无一物
And why should I trust my life to something that isn't there?
那为什么我要把我的性命托付给根本不存在的东西？
Well can you tell me that?
你能告诉我为什么吗？
Answer me!
回答我！
Proog... Proog
Proog……
...you're a sick man!
……你个有病的人！
Stay away from me!
别靠近我！
No! Emo! It's a trap! Emo
不！Emo！那是陷阱！
Hah, it's a trap.
啊，那是陷阱
At the left side you can see the hanging gardens of Babylon!
站在左边你能看到 漂浮的巴比伦花园！
How's that for a trap?
那怎么会是陷阱
No, Emo. Emo
不，Emo
At the right side you can see... ...well guess what...
站在右边你能看到…… ……嗯猜猜看……
...the colossus of Rhodes!
……罗德岛巨像！
No!
不！
The colossus of Rhodes and it is here just for you Proog. Proog.
罗德岛巨像 它在那等你呢，Proog.
It is there...
它在那……
I'm telling you, Emo... Emo
我给你说了，Emo……